figis.com 2015-12-31

# Figi's Internet Privacy Policy

**This policy was last updated and posted in October 2013.**

This Web site is operated by Figi’s Companies, Inc., an affiliate of Mason Companies, Inc. Figi's and its affiliates are committed to respecting your privacy and recognize the need for appropriate protection and management of the personally identifiable and personal information you share with us.

### What is your Internet Privacy Policy?

This Privacy Policy tells you what personally identifiable information and personal information we may collect from our customers and investors, how we may share this information, and how you can limit our sharing of your information. "Personally identifiable information" and "personal information" mean any information by which you can be identified, such as your name, address and telephone number.

As a part of our commitment to your privacy, we support and adhere to the guidelines and practices adopted by the Direct Marketing Association Privacy Promise to American consumers [Direct Marketing Association Privacy Promise to American consumers](https://www.dmachoice.org/static/privacy_policy.php "Direct Marketing Association Privacy Promise to American consumers"). Accordingly, we have agreed to (1) provide customers with notice of their ability to opt out of information exchanges with other marketers; (2) honor customer requests not to have their information transferred to others for marketing purposes; and (3) accept and honor customer requests not to receive solicitations from our brand.

Our Web site may contain links to other Web sites that are not under our control. Those Web sites may have their own policies regarding privacy. We have no control of or responsibility for linked Web sites and provide these links solely for the convenience and information of our visitors. Those Web sites are not subject to this Privacy Policy. You should check the privacy policies, if any, of those individual Web sites to see how the operators of those third-party Web site will utilize your personal information. In addition, this Web site may contain a link to Web sites of our affiliates. The Web sites of our affiliates are not subject to this Privacy Policy, and you should check their individual privacy policies to see how the operators of such Web sites will utilize your personal information.

[top]

### What information do you collect when I visit your Web site?

Generally, our customers can visit our Web site without providing or revealing any personal or personally identifiable information. We receive and store certain types of information whenever visitors interact with our Web site. We may track the Internet domain address from which our visitors visit our Web site and analyze this data for trends and statistics. Unless a visitor to our Web site voluntarily provides personal information to us, each individual customer remains anonymous.

We receive and may store certain personal information that our visitors enter when visiting our Web site or provide to us in other ways. For instance, we collect the information you provide to us when you place an order, register with us, send an e-mail or call us, enter a sweepstakes or contest, subscribe to a service, enroll in a club, request to receive a catalog or direct mail, or participate in a promotion. This information may include your name, shipping/billing address, telephone number, e-mail address, credit card information, product purchases, birth date, gender, occupation, personal interests, and other similar personal or preference data that you provide to us. It may also include information you submit about other people such as the name and address of a gift recipient. Whether or not you provide such information to us is completely your own choice.

[top]

### What is your e-mail policy?

We will not sell, rent, or trade your e-mail address to any unaffiliated third party without your permission. We believe that your e-mail address is personal and should be kept that way. We use your e-mail address to provide better customer service, to facilitate your transactions, and to be able to inform you of internet offers, promotions and updates from Figi’s Companies, Inc. and its affiliates and partners.

[top]

### How do you use my information?

We use the personal and/or personally identifiable information you provide for our internal purposes, such as confirming, fulfilling and tracking your order, subscription or registration, analyzing trends and statistics, informing you of our new products (including products of our affiliates), services and offers, and providing you with information from and about our catalogs and Web site. When you place an order we also use your personal and/or personally identifiable information to fulfill your order. When you place an order, we may also provide your personal and/or personally identifiable information to our marketing partners to enable them to fulfill your order.

From time to time, we may also work with other organizations that we believe are trustworthy and offer products or services that may be of interest to you. In such instances, we might share limited information (such as your name and/or postal address) that we have collected from you, including personally identifiable information, so that such organizations may contact you with offers that may interest you. Be assured, however, that we will not share your information with these organizations if you have requested that we refrain from doing so.

On our Web site, we may provide links to other Web sites that are not owned or controlled by Figi’s Companies, Inc. While we select these associations carefully, we are not responsible for the security and privacy policies or practices of the Web sites accessed through these links. You should refer to these Web sites for their respective privacy and security policies. You access such linked Web sites at your own risk.

To serve you better, we may combine the information you give us online, through our catalogs and order forms; publicly available information; and information we receive from others. We use that combined information to enhance and personalize your experience with us, to communicate with you about our products and events that may be of interest to you, and for other promotional purposes.

Also, we may contract with third-party service providers to provide certain services for our business, such as credit card processing, order processing, fulfillment and management, computer system services, web site operation services, shipping, data management, or promotional services. We provide the information needed for these service providers to perform these services. The information we provide may include some of our customers' personal and personally identifiable information. However, these service providers are not authorized to use any of the information we share with them for any purposes other than to provide services to us.

We may share information that we have collected with governmental agencies and other organizations assisting us in fraud prevention or for investigative purposes. We may do so when permitted or mandated by law; trying to protect against or prevent fraud; attempting to prevent unauthorized or improper transactions; or investigating fraud or improper conduct that has already taken place. In these instances, the information is not provided to these agencies or organizations for marketing or any other unrelated purposes.

Additionally, we may share your e-mail address, name, telephone number, and postal address within the Figi’s Companies, Inc. family (including our parent Mason Companies, Inc. and its affiliates). Also, when you purchase from us through our catalog or our Web site we may need to contact you via phone, e-mail, or mail to address issues specific to your order, even if you have opted to not receive communications from us. From time to time we may also market certain third party services through our site. Should you choose to accept an offer from a third party, we will pass your relevant personal information, including your name, postal address, credit/debit card number and any other required billing information to that specific third party.

Finally, if some or all of the business assets of Figi’s Companies, Inc. are sold or transferred, we generally would transfer the corresponding information regarding our customers and visitors to the purchaser. We also may retain a copy of that information.

### Mobile Marketing

We may distribute advertising messages via text message to mobile devices to customers that have provided us permission via an opt in request. The opportunity to opt out of a specific text message marketing campaign will be made available with the messages we send.

Please note that, with text message campaigns, an opt-in or opt-out request is currently associated only with a specific marketing campaign and a specific mobile phone number. As a result, a request associated with one campaign and phone number will not apply to other campaigns or numbers.

### Aggregate Information

We collect non-personal information about how users navigate through our web site. We aggregate this information in order to improve our site, and we may share this information with our affiliates or other outside companies. This aggregated information does not include individual names or personal data, so it does not identify you or any other customer.

[top]

### What if my information changes?

You may update your registered personal information at any time. This includes your name, password, e-mail, and postal address. You may also manage your mailing preferences and e-mail formats. Update your information or change your mailing preferences.

If at any time you would like us to update your personal information or remove you from our e-mail or postal mailing lists, or if you need assistance with the modification of your information, send us an e-mail with your request or write to us at Figi’s Companies, Inc., Customer Service Dept., 3200 S. Central Avenue, Marshfield, WI 54404.

[top]

### How do I opt out of sharing of my information?

You may opt out of future unaffiliated third-party disclosures of your information. Such opt-out will not affect disclosures otherwise permitted by law including but not limited to: (i) disclosures to affiliates, (ii) disclosures to third-party service providers who provide certain services for our business, such as credit card processing, order processing and fulfillment, computer system services, shipping, data management, or promotional services, (iii) disclosures to third parties as necessary to fulfill your orders and/or requests, (iv) disclosures to governmental agencies or law enforcement departments or otherwise required to be made under applicable law, (v) previously completed disclosures to third parties, or (vi) disclosures to third parties in connection with subsequent orders, contests or promotions you may choose to enter, or third party offers you may choose to accept.

If at any time you need assistance with opting out of the sharing of information with unrelated third parties, send us an e-mail with your request or write to us at Figi's Inc., Opt Out Department, 3200 S. Central Ave., Marshfield, WI 54404 USA.

### Notice to California Residents - Your California Privacy Rights

Under California law, a California resident with whom Charming Shoppes has an established relationship has the right to request certain information with respect to the types of personal information Charming Shoppes has shared with third parties for their direct marketing purposes, and the identities of those third parties, within the immediately preceding calendar year, subject to certain exceptions. All requests for such information must be in writing and sent to: Figi's Companies, Inc. Customer Service Dept. 3200 S. Central Avenue, Marshfield, WI 54404.

This same California law permits Charming Shoppes to provide you, in response to your written request, with a cost-free means to choose not to have your information shared rather than providing the above described information. You may exercise that choice by the means described under "How do I opt out of sharing of my information?"

[top]

### What is your position as to children's privacy?

Our Web site is a general-audience Web site and is not directed to anyone under the age of thirteen ("Children"). We do not seek to solicit information from Children. If Children submit information to us and we know that the individuals submitting the information are indeed Children, we will delete the information as soon as we discover it, we will not use the information for any purpose, and we will not disclose the information to third parties. We urge parents and guardians to participate in their Children's online activities and use parental control or Web filtering technology to supervise Children's access to the Internet.

[top]

### What is your security policy?

Because we all benefit from secure online shopping, we have taken steps to build and manage a system that you can use with confidence. We use sophisticated encryption and authentication tools to protect the security of the personal information that you share with us. The personal information you provide to us is preserved behind a firewall, instead of being directly connected to the Internet. Unfortunately, however, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Once we receive your transmission, we have appropriate security measures in place within our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of the personal information you have provided to us.

We urge you to keep your password for our Web site in a safe place and not divulge it to anyone. Also remember to sign off your account and close your browser window when you have finished your visit to any of our Web sites. This is to ensure that others cannot access your account, especially if you are sharing a computer with someone else or are using a computer in a public place such as a library or Internet cafe.

We use industry-standard efforts such as firewalls, data-encryption methods and password-protected data sources to safeguard the confidentiality of your information. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures to reasonably safeguard and secure the information we collect online. If sensitive data is collected through this Web site, we will encrypt your personal information before it travels over the Internet using industry standards for secure online transactions.

[top]

### What are cookies, and do you use them?

Our Web site uses cookies. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. Generally, we use cookies to remind us who you are; tailor our products and services to suit your personal interests; estimate the number of visitors to our Web sites; track visits to and sales at the stores referenced on our Web site; process your order; track your status in our promotions, contests, and sweepstakes; and/or analyze our customers' visiting patterns. You can generally set your browser to refuse to accept cookies, or to notify you when you are sent a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it. We do not use cookies to store any of your personal or financial information on your computer.

In addition, we use third-party companies to help us gather data to assist us in improving your shopping experience and the quality of our Web site. Some of these companies may use cookies on our behalf to conduct this analysis.

Web beacons may also be used to review how visitors to our Web sites navigate our site or interact with our email advertising. Third-party companies assist in the collection and analysis of this data. These companies may access your email address through these web beacons. Your name, street address or credit card number is not accessed by or shared with other companies through these web beacons.

[top]

### Will your privacy and security policies ever change?

From time to time, our privacy and security practices may change. If we modify our Privacy Policy, in whole or in part, to address these changes, we will indicate when such changes are made by changing the "Last Updated" date at the beginning of this Policy. Those changes will be effective as of the Last Updated date. The new policy will apply to all current and past users of our Web site and will replace any prior policies that are inconsistent. We may change or add to this Policy, so we encourage you to review it periodically.

[top]

### How can I contact you with my suggestions or questions?

To help us improve our privacy and security policies and practices, please send us your questions and feedback. Send us an e-mail.

[top]
